Join Telegram: @lubokvideo - https://t.me/lubokvideo
(wind gusting)
REPORTER: I've just been advised
by our group that we are deploying
six members of law enforcement
and two canine dogs to aid...
REPORTER 2: Another day
of searching in the desert for clues
in the case
of three missing teens.
REPORTER 3: Multiple
law enforcement agencies are here.
REPORTER 4: Well. there's still
volunteers continuing the search.
the satellite images...
REPORTER 5: So anyone
with any information at all...
REPORTER 6:
doubled since yesterday.
As more time goes on.
they're really pushing their resources
to make sure
these teenagers are found.
(gadget beeping. whirring)
(wind chimes)
STEVE: You know.
I read an article.
you wouldn't believe
the living you can make
photographing food.
JOSH: Hey. Dad. what's the secret
to making a great burger?
Well. the first thing you got to do
is you got to get your coals hot.
Super hot. so when you put it on there.
it seals in the juices.
Then you don't flip it but one time.
That's the secret.
GUESTS:
♪ Happy birthday. dear Sophie ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- Make a wish. sweetie. Make a good one.
- JOSH: And many more.
(blowing)
Okay. keep going.
- Keep going. one more! You did it!
- JOSH: Go. go. go!
(all cheering)
CAROLINE:
Come on. Sit down.
JOSH: Imagine that you
were going to talk to grown-up Sophie.
What would you say to yourself?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
JOSH: Can you give Sophie
some advice for the future?
Sophie. when you get older.
you must obey your husband.
- You must obey him.
- JOSH: Gramps!
- What. to Soph?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- Yeah.
- JOSH: Yeah?
You want to do it right now?
Happy birthday. honey.
I love you.
I love you. Sophie.
You're the best.
Your brother is crazy.
but I love him too.
And now he's going to talk to you.
so give me... give me the camera.
- JOSH: No. no. no. I'm the director.
- No. honey. I want the camera now.
No. it's your turn.
Sit down next to your sister. Come on.
- Now you know how I feel.
- Okay.
CAROLINE: All right. I want you to. uh.
say something very sweet to your sister.
A nice wish for her
sixth year of life. Go.
(tape stops)
SOPHIE (narrating): This is how
I remember my brother. How I try to.
Sitting next to me
at my sixth birthday party.
Before anyone knew
our lives were about to change.
That this would be
the last time we were all together.
(jet engines humming)
(indistinct announcement)
(chattering)
- Hey.
- Oh. hey. Hey-
- It's so good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- How was your flight?
- Uh. good. This is Jay.
Jay. this is my dad. Steve.
JAY:
How are you. Steve? Nice to meet you.
What did you pack. Jay?
Are you going to be filming
the whole time?
Yeah. that's. uh...
That's the idea.
STEVE:
You're like Harrison Ford.
Okay. I'm over here in the scam lot.
That's what they do. they scam you.
They've got the public one
that's so far over.
it might as well be in another county.
You go there.
you're going to miss your flight.
And. uh...
they resell the flight and then...
you're shit out of luck
is what you are.
STEVE: So you've got
your own little reality show?
SOPHIE:
It's not a reality show. dad.
- It's a documentary.
- STEVE: Documentary. huh?
- Uh-huh.
- STEVE: Okay.
What's your documentary about?
It's about Josh.
Josh?
(sighs)
REPORTER 5: Anyone
with any information at all.
we're asking you
to please call a special tip line.
REPORTER 2: searching in the desert for
clues in the case of three missing teens.
REPORTER 6: Search efforts
have doubled since yesterday.
As more time goes on.
they're really pushing their resources
to make sure these teenagers are found.
MAN 3: We will continue
to return here until we've
completely exhausted everything
that we think we need to do.
REPORTER 4: There are still volunteers
continuing the search.
uh. and satellite imaging
is ongoing.
REPORTER 7: Arizona State Police
are now in their third week
searching for missing teenagers
Ashley Foster. Mark Abrams.
and Josh Bishop.
STEVE:
Well... sold.
SOPHIE: Yeah.
You don't want to come in?
I... No. I-I better not.
- Just. uh. say hi to mom for me.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Okay. Bye.
(engine revving)
- (Sophie sighs)
- CAROLINE: Well. I like your bangs.
- You're so cute!
- (laughs) Mom!
While you're here.
you've got to go through everything.
- or else I'm giving it to the yard sale.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- I'm fine. okay. I don't need my blankie.
(sighs)
CAROLINE:
Well. as you can see. um...
what's the point of redecorating?
While you're here. I was hoping
you could help me pick up this stuff.
I have a ton of boxes
in the garage
and between the two of us
it shouldn't take us...
Do you still have the tapes?
- This is it. huh?
- CAROLINE: Yeah.
That's the one.
That's... how it all started.
(player whirring)
CAROLINE (on TV):
Oh. it's your turn.
Sit down next to your sister.
(laughs) Come on.
Now you know how I feel.
- JOSH: Okay. Okay.
- CAROLINE: I want you to. uh.
say something very sweet
to your sister.
A nice wish for her
sixth year of life. Go.
Okay. Well. Sophie.
I have one thing to say to you...
STEVE:
Wow. Look at this.
CAROLINE:
Whoa! Is that an airplane?
STEVE:
I don't know.
CAROLINE:
Oh! Josh! Careful!
It's bright.
JOSH:
Hold on.
STEVE:
I don't think it's an airplane.
- CAROLINE: Hmm.
- JOSH: Huh.
STEVE:
Oh. look at that! A fourth one!
They're in formation of some kind.
but they're not really moving.
- CAROLINE: Whoa!
- WOMAN: Whoa!
STEVE:
Five. six. seven lights.
JOSH: Have you guys ever
seen anything like this before?
- STEVE: Hey!
- JOSH: You see that.
You see that? What is that?
- STEVE: on. my God.
- CAROLINE: What is that?
JOSH:
That's definitely not a plane.
STEVE:
That's one object.
- Wow. I've never seen anything like it.
- JOSH: Oh. my God!
- CAROLINE: Honey. zoom in on it.
- JOSH: I'm zooming. Mom.
CAROLINE:
Okay. Okay.
ALL:
Whoa!
- SOPHIA: Whoa!
- CHILD: They're aliens or something.
- JOSH: They're gone.
- CAROLINE: That's weird.
JOSH:
What was that?
I don't know.
- CHILD: Where did they go?
- They're gone.
STEVE: Maybe they... they could have
gone behind the mountain maybe.
- MAN: No. there's no clouds!
- MAN 2: Yeah. we saw the same thing.
- STEVE: That was interesting.
- CAROLINE: That was a show. right?
- MAN: Yeah. right?
- JOSH: Guys. you know what that was?
- Those were UFOs!
- Oh. come on.
JOSH: Those were UFOs!
That's what a UFO is!
CAROLINE: You guys. I think
that's our cue to clean up.
- We gotta... Right? Come on.
- JOSH: Are you kidding me? Dad!
Yeah. it was probably. urn...
I don't know. military.
CAROLINE: Yeah. we've got
to get the presents. Josh.
STEVE:
Josh. put the camera down
- and just help your mother clean up. okay?
- JOSH: Soph...
what do you think that was?
I don't know!
- (jets pass closely overhead)
- (glasses clattering)
(Josh breathing heavily)
Holy moly.
STEVE:
You okay. Soph?
JOSH:
You all right?
SOPHIE:
Yeah.
JOSH:
That was the Air Force. Dad!
Well. I hope it was our Air Force.
JOSH:
Grandpa.
(Josh laughing)
That was amazing!
(theme music playing)
("Twilight Zone" theme plays)
NEWSREADER:
When these lights appeared over Phoenix.
people immediately thought:
UFOs. Outer space.
- We were standing about here?
- Right about here.
- JOSH: Whoa!
- CAROLINE and SOPHIE: Whoa!
They went just over the valley
toward South Mountain
in like a...
What seemed to be a "V" formation.
- It was definitely interesting.
- JOSH: Mm-hmm.
NEWSREADER: So far.
the military hasn't claimed any testing
in the area from nearby
Luke Air Force Base.
which leaves
many residents wondering
"What were those mysterious lights?"
It seemed like the Air Force didn't know
what it was. and if that's true.
then what was it. you know?
I don't know.
And now I'll ask
Officer Stein and his colleagues
to escort the accused
into the room
so that we may all look
upon the guilty party.
Don't get him too close
to me. please.
- (laughter)
- This just goes to show
that you guys are entirely too serious.
(loud laughter)
CAROLINE: No one really took it
that seriously from what I remember.
Except Josh.
SOPHIE:
Would you say he was sort of
single-minded about stuff.
like. once he got an idea?
Yeah. Yeah. there was
no stopping him.
(player whirring)
("X-Files" theme plays)
(crows cawing)
JOSH:
Peeeeeew. Peeeew.
Excuse me. sir. do you have
a second to talk about the...
- Nope.
- Phoenix Lights? Okay. thank you.
- It was just a "V" like this.
- JOSH: And you saw that yourself?
It was just a "V" like that. man.
And we were like...
And we were like.
"Hey. man. check that out. man."
I know... UFOs will come
at us... and attack one day.
- JOSH: You think they'll attack?
- And if that happ...
And if that happens.
we will be prepared.
JOSH:
So. did you see the lights?
No. not personally.
JOSH: Okay. so you saw them on.
like. the news?
- Yeah.
- JOSH: Awesome. Channel 3?
No.
JOSH:
It doesn't matter.
Uh. do you think it was a UFO?
I don't know. Maybe.
- Okay. so. um...
- Can I ask you something now?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: Can I give you some advice?
- JOSH: Umm. sure. Yeah.
- ASHLEY: This is an interview. right?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: So maybe you should ask me
some open-ended questions.
You know. like. things that don't
just warrant yes or no answers.
Just. like. get me to talk...
JOSH:
Okay. yeah. No. Sure.
Is this the same place?
WOMAN: She just had
this charm about her that was electric.
I think because of that
she could get a lot out of people.
people trusted her.
saw her as a confidant.
Jack was kind of pushing
the lawyer thing.
but truly I... I think
Ashley's passion was journalism.
ASHLEY (on TV):
Good morning. Canyon Park High School.
I'm Ashley Foster. CPTV.
Just want to say hello to all the new
freshmen in the building.
Welcome aboard.
I know locker combinations
can be tricky.
but you'll make it through
just like I did.
So just keep trying.
Together. we're a team...
and this is not teamwork.
- (chuckles) That's cute.
- MELISSA: Yeah.
SOPHIE:
What did you guys think of Josh?
We didn't know him.
- MELISSA: Is that Josh's yearbook?
- SOPHIE: Yeah. umm...
Ashley signed it.
- MELISSA: Oh really?
- SOPHIE: Yeah.
- There it is.
- MELISSA: Oh!
Look at that.
(chuckles)
I mean. he was never one of these kids
that came over to the house.
That's it. Josh Bishop.
- Seems like she had a lot of friends.
- Oh. she did. yeah.
She was a charmer.
Have you ever... Have you ever heard
the story of Ezekiel's wheel?
JOSH: Umm...
- It-It's from the Bible.
- JOSH: Oh. Yeah. Definitely not.
Ezekiel describes God
coming down from heaven in a chariot.
It's lighting up the sky.
but all along the outside are eyes.
JOSH:
Why would God need a spaceship?
(laughing)
Exactly.
because he is space.
Yeah.
- JOSH: All right. we're done. It's cool.
- It's done?
- JOSH: Yeah. yeah. yeah.
- Great. Okay. Bye.
JOSH:
Thanks for doing it.
CAROLINE: A very sweet girl.
I met her a few times.
I definitely know that
Josh had a crush on her and...
I'm hoping...
Now I'm going to cry.
I'm hoping she liked him.
Just because they...
spent so much time together.
it would have been nice to know that he.
in his short life.
could experience that.
- SOPHIE: That's Ashley's handwriting.
- CAROLINE: Mm-hmm.
SOPHIE: And how much
do you know about
what Ashley and Josh
were working on?
We certainly didn't know
any of that until...
- later.
- Later.
- It was after.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- We knew very little.
- Mm-hmm.
(player whirring)
We're going to meet
with some astronomers.
- JOSH: Okay.
- They're going to have rocks
and all different kinds
of stuff to show us.
so we've got to be prepared. and we need
to make sure that we're on our "A" game.
JOSH:
What does our "A" game mean?
We just have to be professional.
But I'm feeling... I feel like I've been
pretty professional so far. thank you.
I don't think
I'm exactly amateur hour.
I know. but I-I guess
I'm just a little nervous.
I want everything to go good.
Well. do you have
any questions prepared?
I have a ton. they're in my backpack.
Do you have my backpack by the way?
JOSH:
Yeah. I do.
MAN: Have you ever held
a meteorite before?
I'll start with this one.
ASHLEY:
Whoa! (laughing)
MAN: We get phone calls about UFOs
kind of frequently.
JOSH: So when the Phoenix Lights happened.
were people calling and asking?
Uh... yeah. they were.
- A few.
- ASHLEY: He shot the footage.
- Oh. you shot the footage?
- (laughing) That's right. yeah.
Oh. congratulations!
Can you learn to focus?
- (both laughing)
- There you go.
STEVE (on TV): They're in
a formation of some kind.
but they're not really moving.
Okay. that's more likely flares.
(radio chatter)
DUN: The flares are probably
fifty to a hundred miles away.
So you don't see the smoke. You just see
a bright light that just hangs there
because of the parachute
to hold them in place.
ASHLEY: Would you say you're
a hundred percent sure it's not
or you're ninety-nine percent sure
and still open to the possibility?
No. I'm a hundred percent sure
that-that-that... that that's what it was.
- Oh! A jet.
- DON: It's an F-18.
- JOSH: What was that?
- ASHLEY: What did you say. Don?
- F-18.
- ASHLEY: How do you know?
MARK:
He's got the ear for it.
ASHLEY: All right. I got
as close as I could.
There's this creepy guy
who was just staring me down.
I think he was about
to call security on me.
JOSH:
You actually believe it was the Air Force.
- You believe that...
- I do not.
- You believe the bearded...
- I don't know what I believe yet!
- I'm open...
- JOSH: The bearded Galileo Society
of Phoenix. Arizona. I'm disappointed.
You're no longer a producer.
ASHLEY:
I am absolutely a producer!
(whispering)
I think I found the section.
JOSH:
"Ancient UFO sightings."
ASHLEY:
Check this out. Petroglyphs.
JOSH:
That's totally a spaceship.
Isn't this that Bible thing
you were talking about?
ASHLEY:
Ezekiel's wheel.
JOSH: Wait. I know
what this reminds me of.
It's like the machine
at the end of Contact.
ASHLEY:
I love that movie.
Okay to go.
(shuddering)
Okay to go-
- JOSH: Initiate drop sequence.
- Okay to go!
Oh. my God. Oh. my God. I think
I'm going through a Wormhole!
(laughing)
Okay-
JOSH: I don't want
to seem ungrateful for all the help.
but what are we doing here?
We should be. like.
breaking into Area-51.
ASHLEY: Can you tell us
your name and what you do here?
TONY: My name is Tony Duncan.
I'm from the Apache Nation.
For the most part.
we do a lot of story-telling.
A lot of our stories
of creation talk about
how at one time
we were up in the lights.
up in the sky world. so maybe it was
one of our peoples up there.
ASHLEY:
So. you saw the lights last week?
I didn't see them.
I didn't see them... that exact time.
um. but I just heard
everyone's different stories.
But then eventually. you know.
I seen all the footage of it.
I first thought of the star people.
"That must be them. our relatives."
ASHLEY: You said
you didn't see them that exact time.
- What did you mean?
- Yeah. Actually. um...
way before the lights
that were seen in Phoenix.
my friend that I grew up with...
His name is Pony...
We actually seen some lights
in the same way.
but they were a lot closer.
and we followed them.
- ASHLEY: Wait.
- JOSH: You saw the same formation?
Yeah. yeah. They were in the sky.
and they were actually...
They'd be here and then
they would take off really fast.
and they would move around.
and it was really exciting.
and then it went way out into the field.
Like. we were running way out
into the field for a long time.
- our legs were getting all scratched up.
- (Ashley laughs)
Eventually. it just took off.
Away. high upward. Just...
We couldn't see it anymore.
Uh. but we still talk
about that. Pony and I.
Uh. but that was off over in Salt River.
in the Salt River Reservation.
ASHLEY:
The bus definitely doesn't go that far.
JOSH:
That's where we're going.
ASHLEY: Well. that's where we're
deciding if we should go.
to be more accurate.
JOSH: Are you serious?
What. are you scared of sky people?
Of being taken to the spirit world
- with the Anasazi.
- Well. I kind Of believed him.
JOSH:
Please come.
I need my producer. you know.
(laughs)
JOSH: I think it would make
a really sick documentary.
I'll show it to colleges or... somebody.
How do we get there?
(laughs)
(doorbell rings)
JOSH: That's for me.
CAROLINE: Okay. Mark!
- MARK: Mrs. Bishop.
- CAROLINE: I haven't seen you in so long.
- I know. how are you?
- Good. how are you?
Hey.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
- Did you do something with your hair?
- CAROLINE: Oh. Just got it done.
- JOSH: Are you serious?
- Thanks for noticing.
- No problem.
- JOSH: Can you stop flirting with my mom?
I'm not flirting with your mom.
She does look pretty good though.
JOSH: All right. go.
And let's not forget
our most important piece
of equipment on this journey...
(taps)
my 1994 Grand Jeep Cherokee.
Six-cylinder engine.
blood-red finish. roof racks...
16-inch clearance. perfect for maneuvering
over any desert...
(thump)
JOSH: Sorry.
NEWSREADER (on TV):
phenomenon has returned.
- JOSH: Oh. shit.
- For the second time in one week.
mysterious lights have been spotted
over the Phoenix area...
- Yo. Mark! Look at this!
- This time. over the suburb of Mesa.
The sightings fascinated residents.
MAN (on TV): It was completely silent.
You couldn't hear it.
but you knew it was there.
It was just massive. it was big.
NEWSREADER: Eye-witnesses
describe what they saw as being identical
to the glowing orbs that passed
through the area earlier this week...
Is that them?
Are those your aliens?
A mysterious "V" formation
that flew from west to east.
- The video you're seeing right now...
- JOSH: Dude. I know where this is.
Captured in Mesa
about ten miles from the...
JOSH: Wait. this is it. here on the right.
Right. right. right. right! Go!
- Go. go. go. go. go!
- MARK: Shit. Let me know
- a little earlier next time
- (Josh laughs)
MARK:
Jeez. man.
Dang.
(car doors closing)
JOSH: This is it. This is where
they were. right over that ridge.
MARK: Well...
whatever they were.
they're long gone now.
JOSH:
Dude.
Well. dude. check this out.
Somebody's up there.
You do realize we gotta get up
in. like. six hours. right?
JOSH: Dude.
we're almost to the top.
MARK:
All right.
Whoa!
Get down.
Dude. kill the light.
What are you doing? Josh?
(switch clicks)
(whispering)
Josh. let's get the hell out of here.
JOSH: Just hang on.
MARK:
Man. those are cops up there.
JOSH:
Dude. there's no plates.
MARK:
I don't care. let's go.
They're just cops.
JOSH: Dude. cops don't walk around in
the middle Of the night with telescopes.
They're looking for it.
MARK:
What?
- JOSH: The UFO.
- MARK: Josh. I don't care. Let's go.
- JOSH: That's what they're looking for.
- MARK: Oh. my God.
- MAN: Hey!
- JOSH: Oh shit!
MARK:
Run. bitch!
Run! Come on!
JOSH: Okay. so this is the first sighting
right above South Mountain.
This is the second.
And this is where we're going.
right in the flight path of the first two.
Nobody knows about this.
I told you.
I guess we'll find out tomorrow.
MAN:
This was an unusual case.
SOPHIE: What do you mean
it was unusual? In what sense?
Uh. well... it's very uncommon to have
three kids go missing at the same time.
- Just because there were three of them?
- There were three. yeah.
It is usually one. maybe two.
boyfriend-girlfriend.
but the fact that there were three.
you know. set it outside
of the norm.
(chattering)
SOPHIE: What did you guys use
to get to drink?
MAN: I always got lemonade but Mark.
he'd always go for a suicide.
All the way down.
Dash of everything.
SOPHIE: Do you remember
the night that you got the call?
Sure. Yeah. Um...
I was in my first year at ASU.
and I got a call late at night
from my mom
saying that Mark hadn't come home.
My dad was convinced that I'd taken him
to some frat party and gotten him drunk.
He was pissed off.
(police radio chatter)
He was even more pissed
than Ashley's dad.
if you can believe that.
My morn told me that if I just got
them home ASAP. I wouldn't get in trouble.
They just... they refused to believe me.
I didn't realize at the time that I was
the last reasonable explanation
that they had
before they started to freak out for real.
OFFICER (on radio):
Officer...
DISPATCHER (on radio):
Is someone there?
OFFICER: Possible 11-24
on the side of the highway.
(dispatcher speaks indiscernibly)
OFFICER:
No. no one inside.
- Copy that. 11-24.
- DISPATCHER: 10-4.
(engine starts)
SOPHIE: Should I put
my phone in airplane mode?
PILOT (over headset):
It won't affect the flight at all
- if you don't put it in.
- SOPHIE (over headset): All right.
- I use that on planes.
- PILOT: Yeah. that's bull crap.
SOPHIE: The reason I wanted to talk
to you was because you were involved
- in the search for my brother.
- I was.
Um. can you tell me
a little bit about... about that?
Strange case.
KEVIN:
That's where the car was found.
Right down there?
SOPHIE: Do you think someone could have
forced them off the road?
MAN:
It's possible. but I doubt it.
It seems like they left
the car here intentionally.
SOPHIE:
What do you mean. "intentionally"?
Oh. the car was parked
perfectly in line.
so it didn't seem like
they were in a rush or anything.
The doors were locked.
We didn't find the keys.
It was functional. It... it ran.
It wasn't like it ran out of gas
or the battery died out there.
They were able to start it up.
WALTER: And we found
some beers in the car.
SOPHIE: Some beers?
Like. they were drinking?
Yeah. Just a couple of beers. We really
don't know if that means anything.
There were traces of blood.
and we think it was Mark's.
And your brother's camera. of course.
CAROLINE: This is the one
they found in the car.
MARK: The Diamondbacks are
the snakes that you want to look out for.
Some dude died.
I guess he was climbing over.
like. a ridge
and it struck.
and it hit him in the neck.
- (honks)
- JOSH: You dick!
MARK:
What?
JOSH: Are you serious?
What about her parents. huh?
MARK: You're the one
who wants to hit the road.
JOSH: You want to get in trouble
before we even leave?
- God.
- Now she comes out.
JOSH:
Well. I guess it worked.
It's 7:30 in the morning.
you dicks.
MARK:
All right. well. there's a lot of dicks
getting thrown at the driver right now.
- (Ashley laughs) What?
'AH right. you guys ready?
- Josh. do you have all the equipment?
- Can you move your camera?
JOSH: Yeah. no.
we're good. we're good.
Are you sure
we shouldn't double check?
'Cause once we're gone.
we're gone.
- Okay. go. go. Please drive.
- MARK: What?
- It's just I don't want to talk to my dad.
- JOSH: He looks like a sweet man.
ASHLEY:
Yeah. until you meet him.
Wait. when do you guys
have to be home by?
MARK:
My parents aren't as concerned.
My mom just like won't go
to sleep until I'm home.
Different when you're a girl...
- MARK: No. no. a hundred percent.
- With two men.
- ASHLEY: Hey look! Look. Josh.
- It would say Interstate.
Look at this. It looks like
those petroglyphs in that book.
- MARK: Those were clearly made...
- ASHLEY: Quick. shoot that.
MARK:
by alien spacecraft.
(country music plays on radio)
♪ Arizona. take off your hobo shoes ♪
♪ Arizona. hey. won'tcha go my way ♪
MARK: I can tell 'em
a little something.
(rapping)
♪ Unh. Arizona. Unh ♪
♪ So hot and fresh.
giving me a boner ♪
♪ Unh. rock and roller ♪
♪ Unh. bowler. Coca-Cola ♪
♪ Solar plexus ♪
♪ 'Cause we're better
than Texas ♪
♪ 'Cause we're so big
and fierce ♪
♪ Call us T-Rexes ♪
♪ Look at our faces.
I know you wanna sex us! ♪
Whoo!
♪ Arizona. take off
your rainbow shades ♪
♪ Arizona.
have another look at the world... ♪
WALTER: What happened between here
and when they left the car...
you see that's the mystery.
Wouldn't know if it was
a couple of hours or maybe a whole day.
That's the hole we're trying to fill.
REPORTER: Another day in the desert.
searching for clues
for three missing teens.
So the ground search was odd.
'cause it turned up almost nothing.
Normally in a case like that
where people turn up missing
and then we find a vehicle.
urn. they locate something.
And there were no effective trails
that led us one direction or another
and even when they used
their dogs out there.
REPORTER '3: After two days of searching.
a small army of law officers
are setting up camp
alongside a desert highway.
KEVIN: People that are
on the ground tell you that.
"Hey. the one gal has
a bright yellow shirt or something."
So that's something that you're gonna
try to key on as looking down.
And you just go back and forth.
kind of like mowing the yard.
It looks very flat from the air.
but when you get down on the ground
and you start walking around
even the smallest bit of terrain. there is
a lot of... lot of places they could be.
Now anyone with any information
about this case
is asked to call a special tip line...
KEVIN: If you'd have asked me
at the front end. "Are we going
to find these kids." I would have said.
"Yeah. Oh. yeah. we'll find them."
Three things to look for.
Three shirts.
I don't want to be morbid.
but three bodies.
I mean. there's-there's more...
There's more to search for.
We just found nothing.
SOPHIE: So if you were to speculate.
what do you think happened to them?
Maybe if I wasn't
on camera or something.
I think maybe I could give you
some opinions.
but. um. it's hard to speculate.
SOPHIE: Okay. so what
do you think happened? (laughing)
KEVIN: There's potentially some sort
of relationship issue.
One boy likes the girl.
and the girl likes the other boy.
and the two boys find out
about the issue.
PIROUZNIA: Maybe somebody
came along and picked them up
and could have taken them somewhere.
but they should have surfaced.
WALTER:
Foul play is possible.
but it's very tough
if only one person did it.
It's very difficult to hold three people.
you know. together.
KEVIN: It could just be someone
out there that's running some dope.
SOPHIE: They were just
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
KEVIN: Wrong place wrong time.
Stumble upon something that was five miles
from where they were.
where the vehicle was located.
and they were driven to that loca...
Like I said.
we didn't find anything.
so who knows what happened?
Hard to speculate.
ASHLEY:
How did you meet Josh?
MARK: I feel weird talking about this.
'cause I know he's gonna watch it later.
We met. uh...
We met in church actually.
- ASHLEY: Really?
- MARK: Yeah.
Everybody called Josh. "Ginger."
and they were making fun Of him.
like. calling him "Ginger"
because of his red hair.
but when I was little. I didn't know
"Ginger“ was a name for redheads.
I just thought it was a nickname.
like. specifically for Josh.
So I just thought the coolest kid at
Sunday school... everybody knew who he was.
so I went out of my way
to hang out with him.
- (Ashley chuckles)
- That's when we started becoming friends.
ASHLEY:
Oh. nice.
ASHLEY: I just got some B-roll.
but I got some really cool cactuses...
JOSH: Were you guys filming me
while I was asleep?
- ASHLEY: No.
- MARK: No. Never.
- (Josh laughs sarcastically)
- ASHLEY: Okay. a little bit.
- MARK: Can you put your seatbelt back on?
- ASHLEY: Yeah.
- MARK: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: Literally nothing out here.
(shouts)
Hello!
MARK: You're gonna get
your head taken off by one of those.
- I wanna live here.
- MARK: You wanna live here?
Yeah. Maybe.
- Whoa. whoa. watch out!
- (thuds)
- JOSH: God!
- MARK (chuckles): Sorry. guys. My bad.
- Whoa. check that out.
- JOSH: What? What is it?
MARK:
Dead animal. A coyote?
- JOSH: Is it two?
- MARK: Yeah.
- Yeah. it is.
- JOSH: Hold on. this camera sucks.
(static)
- SOPHIE: So that's it?
- CAROLINE: That's it.
That's the last he shot.
SOPHIE: Hang on.
So Josh went all the way out there
and then just didn't shoot
anything past the road?
Doesn't that seem weird to you?
WALTER: I always thought
it was a little odd.
SOPHIE:
Why? Why odd?
Well. your brother...
He seemed to have that camera
glued to his face all the time.
It-It just didn't make
any sense to leave it behind.
SOPHIE: So do you think
maybe they had a second camera?
Like. is that a possibility?
I thought about that.
I-I still think your brother
would have had that with him.
PIROUZNIA:
I know Ashley had access
to those camera equipment
and could check out.
but I don't remember anything
being unaccounted for at the time.
We... we ran that thread out
as far as we could.
and we just couldn't take it.
and law enforcement
couldn't take it anywhere either.
SOPHIE: So that's what the kids would
have been using back in '97. right?
It's a little before my time.
but yeah. probably.
SOPHIE: Do you still have any
of those old cameras laying around?
Yeah.
ASHLEY (on TV):
I'm Ashley Foster. CPTV.
Just want to say hello to all
the new freshmen in the building.
LUISA:
Where did you get this?
SOPHIE:
This was found in Mark Abrams' Jeep
after he went missing
with Ashley and with my brother.
We think Josh had
a second camera with him on the trip.
If he did have one.
it most likely came from the school.
so I was wondering if you thought Ashley
could have checked one out from here.
like. maybe she used
a different name?
It's possible. but like I said.
it was before I started.
Would there have been. like.
a logbook or records of that?
- Like. stuff that might have been...
- It's been 20 years.
I'm so sorry I can't be
of more help to you.
Even if they had a second camera.
it just... it went missing with them.
Just another dead end. you know?
REPORTER (on TV):
And new developments tonight.
Rescuers were forced to call off
their search for three missing teens.
saying there was "no new
credible evidence or clues
to guide the search."
It's like they've been written off.
They've been... my son and his friends
have been abandoned
by the police department.
PIROUZNIA: All the efforts
by law enforcement
to develop some evidence
as to what happened.
they were pretty...
Well. they were negative.
They could never go anywhere
with the case.
I think if they had kids. they'd want
somebody looking for their kid.
(camera clicks)
Dear Ashley.
I know that you're alive...
and that you can hear
my voice right now.
You can't imagine how much your father
and I miss you... and love you.
Every night. I have a dream
that I come downstairs
and you're sitting at the table
like you were never even gone.
I know this means something.
I know it means that you...
are still alive.
(emotionally) Your father and I
will never give up hope.
I love you. Ashley.
Please come home.
MELISSA: I wanted a funeral...
but Jack wouldn't have it.
So. here we are.
The bench was a compromise?
Yep. That's what marriage is about.
It's... uh... Sophie. I don't...
I don't think your brother's alive.
I-I... I don't think...
I don't think he is.
I think something would have developed.
SOPHIE:
Jay. get in here.
- JAY: What's up?
- Have you seen this?
If you'd been here ten years ago
and standing out here and looking up there
at the lights and the view. um.
you would have been astounded.
You would have been amazed.
- JAY: Is that the governor?
- Yeah.
Twenty years ago.
he said the lights were a joke.
He had a whole press conference
making fun of them.
And now he's saying
he saw the lights that night.
MAN (on laptop):
I got four of 'em.
He's basically admitting he lied.
REPORTER: The former governor.
a Vietnam Air Force veteran.
had never publicly
acknowledged seeing it until now
And I suspect that...
unless the Defense Department
proves this otherwise.
that it was probably some form
of an alien spacecraft.
And I think as a public figure. you have
to be very careful about what you say.
because people can have
pretty emotional reactions.
JAY:
Is that him?
Okay. follow me
and just keep rolling.
Excuse me. Mr. Garland?
Hi. I'm Sophie Bishop.
We spoke on the phone.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
Right. I just have
a couple questions.
You worked for the governor from 1992
until he resigned in '97. is that right?
Sophie. I don't know anything
about your brother.
Okay. what about the Phoenix Lights?
On March 15th. 1997. you went on TV.
and you said that
they were military flares.
Did you see the Governor
on CNN saying that was a lie?
You were his press secretary at the time.
Listen. I really am very sorry
about your brother.
We were just trying not to create a panic.
Who told you to lie?
I mean. what if Josh
was on to something?
We always assumed he got lost
or kidnapped or...
murdered but what if...
JAY:
What if he got abducted by aliens?
(chuckles)
Jesus. I sound like him. don't I?
JAY:
So... now what?
I don't know.
I don't know what
we're doing here anymore.
CAROLINE:
Can't believe you're leaving.
It feels like you just got here.
SOPHIE:
Can I ask you one more question?
Why did you and Dad decide
to call it quits?
Sweetheart.
everyone's divorced now.
I want to know.
Was it Josh's disappearance
or would you guys have
split up anyway?
- ASHLEY (on TV): Hello!
- (Mark chuckles)
MARK: You're going to get
your head taken off by one of those.
ASHLEY:
I want to live here.
- MARK: You want to live here?
- ASHLEY: Yeah. Maybe.
Josh. you want to stop here?
- STEVE: Well. how is she?
- SOPHIE: She's good.
Just getting ready
for the big move. you know.
Well. please tell her. you know.
if she needs any help or anything.
she should call me.
Somebody knows what happened.
JAY: Mark didn't just
wander off into the desert.
He didn't get lost.
That never made sense to me.
SOPHIE:
If Josh hadn't gone missing...
do you think you and Mom
would still be together?
Yeah.
What'd she say?
Sweetheart. what happened was
your brother went missing.
Completely missing.
And it took over our lives.
REPORTER: resources to make sure
these teenagers are found.
If that's true. then what was it.
you know? I don't know.
CAROLINE:
Is Josh dead? Is he alive?
Was he suffering?
Our relationship became about
all those questions.
and your father.
he couldn't do it anymore
and still be the man
that I fell in love with.
and I couldn't do it anymore
and still be his wife.
(jets pass closely overhead)
STEVE: Everybody keeps criticizing me
for. you know. not dealing with it.
I was the only one who was
still out there
trying to figure out
what happened to your brother.
SOPHIE: Do you think there's ever going to
be a point where you can let it go. Dad?
I mean. show... show me his body.
- Good to see you.
- SOPHIE: Love you.
- I love you. too.
- Okay.
All right. Do me a favor:
When you get home. give me a call. okay?
- Okay.
- Let me know you got in okay.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- We're going to see you Christmas?
- Yeah. I'll see you Christmas.
- Okay.
- All right.
- SOPHIE: Love you.
I love you.
- Bye. Dad.
- Bye.
LUISA (on voicemail):
Hi. Sophie. this is Luisa. Luisa Moreno.
We spoke several months ago
at Canyon Park High.
Um... just call me back when you can.
SOPHIE: Hi.
- Thank you so much for meeting me.
- Yeah.
Did you have a hard time
finding the place?
- No. no. not at all.
- Great.
This place has been on the books
since the late '70s.
Pretty much anything old
or outdated gets thrown in here.
I was throwing away
some garbage over the weekend
and just saw it sitting in the drawer.
Somebody must have thrown it
in here and forgotten about it.
- Can I take this?
- Oh. it's yours.
DAN:
I know you're excited about this. but...
I just don't want you
to get your hopes up. you know?
SOPHIE:
Yeah. I know.
Is that a tape?
- Be careful.
- JAY: I know.
Okay-
- SOPHIE: That's Ashley's handwriting.
- JAY: Really?
Holy shit.
SOPHIE:
Hit play.
I'm going to let you do this.
All right. you ready?
JAY:
Ready.
Soph? Sophie?
SOPHIE:
Hi.
Sophie Bishop.
I have an appointment with Captain Groves.
IDs please.
(helicopter approaching)
Just pull over to the side. ma'am.
I need you to wait right over there.
Okay. Is there a problem?
We should have an appointment.
Yes ma'am.
I need you to wait right over there.
Okay-
SOPHIE:
What's it been. like an hour?
That's him.
Okay. uh. just stay here.
keep it low.
(car door alarm beeping)
- Miss Bishop?
- Hi.
Hi there.
So we can do the interview
out here or in your office.
whichever you prefer.
It's not gonna happen.
(speaks indiscernibly)
Okay. but... when we spoke on the phone.
you said that it was fine.
so I guess I'm just wondering what
happened that made you change your mind.
I understand.
- (speaks indiscernibly)
- (helicopter approaching)
Did you watch the footage?
- (helicopter passes overhead)
- (speaks indiscernibly)
Drive safe.
JAY:
You okay?
Yeah. I just honestly
wasn't expecting that.
JAY:
What did he say?
He said. "Don't let that footage get out."
(scoffs)
JAY:
What do you want to do?
What do you think Josh would do?
(static)
JOSH: This is gonna be rad.
Dude.
- MARK: Yeah.
- JOSH: Look at its eye.
- MARK (chuckles): Yeah.
- JOSH: This camera is amazing.
- MARK: Yo. don't get too close.
- JOSH: It smells burnt.
MARK:
It's like males competing for females.
JOSH:
They have the same burns.
Countless stories when UFOs
have been sighted about.
like. animal experimentation.
MARK:
Uh-huh. Yeah. yeah.
They just got cooked by the sun.
- ASHLEY: Woo!
- MARK: Oh shit.
This way.
- MARK: Obviously I'm joking.
- ASHLEY: You just said you look
like older Leo.
People told me that
when Romeo and Juliet came out.
ASHLEY:
What. they said that you...
MARK: That literally made me
more popular in school.
JOSH:
What are you guys talking about?
- What?
- JOSH: What are you guys talking about?
- MARK: You.
- (Ashley laughs)
JOSH:
Just at the top of that ridge.
We wouldn't be able
to see anything from down here.
MARK: Not like we're gonna see
anything up there. either.
JOSH (groans):
Don't be that guy.
We don't need that guy.
You remember where we parked
the car. right?
MARK: Uh... yeah.
It's... that a-way.
- ASHLEY: Ooh. Josh.
- MARK: Oh shit.
Come look at this.
- JOSH: What do you got?
- ASHLEY: Whoa.
Petroglyphs.
JOSH: Oh!
ASHLEY:
Guess this means we're on the right track.
MARK:
Wow. Ancient graffiti.
Now what you see below me
are Native American petroglyphs.
They were probably put here
hundreds of years ago
by the Apache.
They were native to these lands.
very adept at living
in these mountainous regions.
Uh...
the spiral shape
that you see below us...
Historians aren't quite sure
what it could have represented.
It could have represented
ripples in water.
things that they saw in the sky.
And... that's pretty much it.
Petroglyphs.
ASHLEY:
Please be careful.
(yelps)
(laughs)
- You get that?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- It look steep?
- Yeah.
ASHLEY:
You guys are idiots.
ASHLEY: Ah. I should not
have smoked that cigarette.
(imitating gunfire)
ASHLEY:
Whoa.
How far do you want us
to go. Josh?
JOSH:
Just keep going.
ASHLEY: I'm wheezing.
I'm out of breath.
Whoa.
- You rolling?
- JOSH: Yeah.
Check this out.
Oh. shit.
JOSH: Where'd you get those?
Ask Diane Sawyer over there.
ASHLEY: I got it from a guy
at the gas station.
Here. He had a crush on you
or something.
I just used my eyes.
- Yeah. Dude. no. no. Do not film this.
- MARK: We have two more in here.
(Ashley laughing)
is Josh filming this?
- (Ashley laughing)
- Whoa.
Will you please be as careful as possible
with that on a cliff edge.
ASHLEY (laughing):
Sorry.
- Where's Mark?
- He's taking a leak.
Oh. you didn't want to go with him?
Shut up.
- What are you doing?
- It's my turn to interview you.
- This is...
- See how you like it.
It's not a Hitchcock movie. you know.
The director isn't in this one.
MARK: You guys playing
Truth or Dare up here?
- ASHLEY: Want to play Truth or Dare?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: You go first.
- MARK: You actually want to play?
- ASHLEY: Yeah. why not?
- JOSH: Come on.
- JOSH: I've got a couple beers in me.
- Uh... dare.
ASHLEY: Okay.
I dare you to tell the truth.
That is not how you play the game.
- JOSH: It's fair enough.
- ASHLEY: That is how I play the game.
JOSH: What's. uh... what's the deal
with you and Debbie Gomez?
De-Debbie Gomez?
MARK: Why?
JOSH: Well. the old rumor mill's
been. you know...
We hang out sometimes.
Like. I don't...
JOSH:
You guys play tennis or go golfing?
Why are you being a dick. dude?
Like. we hang out.
- Like. it's not...
- ASHLEY: Why didn't you invite her here?
MARK: I don't know.
I didn't want to make it weird.
JOSH: What do you mean.
"make it weird"?
Why would that be weird?
MARK: I didn't want to make it
like a double date.
- Wait. now that's weird.
- JOSH: Oh. come on. man.
ASHLEY: All right.
we cannot stay here forever.
We need to go as soon
as the sun dips down.
JOSH: Just hold on and enjoy it
for a second. please.
I just want to get this.
It's gorgeous.
- MARK: Josh.
- What?
- MARK: What is that?
- JOSH: What?
- ASHLEY: What?
- MARK: That.
No. no. what is that?
- Ashley.
- ASHLEY: Whoa. what'?
- Wait. Mark. isn't that... what?
- MARK: It's just kind of sitting there.
ASHLEY: Wait.
isn't the Luke Air Force Base over there?
- JOSH: Yeah.
- MARK: Maybe.
JOSH: Probably just something
from the Air Force Base.
- Maybe a helicopter.
- MARK: You're the one looking for UFOs.
- ASHLEY: No. that's not a helicopter.
- MARK: I'm just pointing it out.
ASHLEY:
We'd hear it if it was a helicopter.
JOSH:
Hold on.
- ASHLEY: Wait. Okay. you guys.
- MARK: Think it's a fighter jet?
- MARK: No. that's not a fighter jet.
- ASHLEY: Don't get ahead of yourself.
It's just a light.
MARK: It's not.
You'd hear it. you'd hear it.
ASHLEY:
What? Oh. my God.
- JOSH: Okay. Okay.
- (explosion)
- (Ashley gasps)
- MARK: Whoa!
- MARK: Holy shit!
- What!
Josh. did you get that?
JOSH: Hold on.
MARK: Oh...
- What was that?
- ASHLEY: I don't...
- Wait. tell me you got that on camera.
- JOSH: Yes!
MARK:
Can you play that back?
- ASHLEY: Oh. my God! Josh.
- MARK: Guys. stop. stop. stop.
ASHLEY:
Wait. Josh. seriously though.
JOSH: This is
the greatest day of my life.
ASHLEY: Oh. my... did you know
that was gonna happen?
Here. give me that back.
MARK: Did you know
that was gonna happen?
Is Luke Air Force Base that way?
Luke Air Force Base is that way.
but that's not Air Force.
- MARK: How do you know?
- ASHLEY: You don't know that.
JOSH:
Because it's not 2150.
(Mark and Ashley laugh)
JOSH:
Come back.
- MARK: All right. man.
- ASHLEY: Twenty minutes.
MARK: Get like a last pan
or whatever. Let's go.
Dude. come on.
I'm happy for you. let's go.
- JOSH: Just ten more minutes?
- MARK: You've done that twice.
ASHLEY: Do you know
how hard it's gonna be
to walk through this canyon
in the dark?
JOSH: I don't see
what the problem is. okay?
- You know the way back.
- ASHLEY: It's already dark.
(arguing over each other)
MARK: The problem is that it starts
to get really dark and really cold.
and she has a curfew.
and I still have to drive.
- ASHLEY: Please.
- MARK: Come on.
Cut. We gotta go.
ASHLEY:
All right. we're leaving.
JOSH: What if we get
arrested by. like.
the Air Force or something?
MARK: That would actually be
the scariest situation.
JOSH: Like our parents
don't ever find out.
like. what's going to happen
to us.
The Air Force just takes us away
or something.
MARK: That'd be so sad.
JOSH: My mom would think I was just
in my room playing with the camera.
MARK: They wouldn't notice?
They wouldn't... like. it would take
a couple years I think.
My parents are noticing right now.
Oh...
- (screams)
- You good?
- Yeah.
- JOSH: Mark.
- Mark!
- Sorry.
- ASHLEY: Whoa.
- MARK: Give it to me.
Give me that.
Give me the UFO.
- Ah!
JOSH: After tonight.
you can be producer.
assistant director.
You know what?
If you're lucky. we can talk "co."
- We can what?
- JOSH: We can talk "co."
- All right.
- JOSH: Co-director.
MARK:
He's three years older than me.
JOSH:
His brother voted for Dole.
- MARK: No. he didn't.
- Bob Dole? Really?
JOSH:
Yes. he did. Your brother's a moron.
MARK: My brother's... are you kidding me?
He's an... he's an engineering student.
He's an engineering student.
He's actually very smart.
He's gonna be president one day.
- ASHLEY: Is this a dead end?
- MARK: No. you gotta keep going through.
ASHLEY:
Are you sure it's not a dead end?
- MARK: I'm positive it's not a dead end.
- ASHLEY: All right.
MARK:
We walked through here in the daytime.
- JOSH: Does it usually get this tight?
- MARK: Yeah.
We're good.
It goes on for a while.
I'm gonna be in so much trouble.
- MARK: You guys need help?
- JOSH: It's worth being in trouble.
Do you understand what we've seen today?
Yeah. but I can push it like
an hour. but any longer. it's...
We would've noticed these
on the way in for sure.
I don't remember these.
JOSH: Yeah. I for sure
would have noticed these.
Mark. are you sure we passed...
ASHLEY:
Mark where are we going?
MARK:
Hold on. I'll be super sure. hold on.
ASHLEY: Are you sure
we're going the right way?
Yes!
JOSH:
Why can't you just use the stars. man?
- Josh.
- MARK: No. it's this way.
- ASHLEY: Are you positive?
- Yep.
ASHLEY:
All right.
- JOSH: Do you guys not hear that?
- BOTH: What?
- MARK: What?
- ASHLEY: Josh. come on.
- JOSH: Everything just looks like rocks.
- MARK: I know where we are.
Yeah. but you keep going
left then right. then left then right.
You keep complaining
about us being late. so can we go?
I know exactly where we're going.
JOSH: I mean. who else
are we gonna listen to anyway?
(sighs)
Okay. let's go. What way?
MARK: Hold on.
Just stop moving. Let me...
look first.
(horn blares in distance)
- (gasps)
- MARK: Well...
- JOSH: I definitely heard that.
- I just heard something.
Guys. Get down.
(whispers)
Get down.
Mark. get down.
(horn blares in distance)
(distant rumbling)
- ASHLEY: What is that?
- JOSH: It could be a train.
I-I... I didn't see any tracks out here.
MARK:
Shh. Just listen.
(horn blares in distance)
(distant rumbling)
MARK:
Okay. we're almost back.
- ASHLEY: Let's get the hell out of here.
- MARK: Let's go.
- ASHLEY: Everybody walk faster.
- MARK: Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey. It's okay.
- Ash. it's all right.
- ASHLEY: We need to get out of here now.
MARK:
I know. Just calm down.
Josh...
do you recognize any of this?
- Give me the compass.
- Do you want to try'?
- JOSH: Guys!
- Yes! Give me the compass.
Get us home.
- Okay. I will. I will!
- You do it.
(sighs)
Okay. so... we came from this way.
We got this way.
- It's definitely not this way.
- JOSH: Mark?
- Mark. where you going?
- MARK: Just stay there.
- JOSH: Mark. where you going?
- I'm gonna find the car from up here!
JOSH: You're not gonna see anything
up there. it's pitch black.
ASHLEY: Hey. Josh?
Can you come look at this?
JOSH:
What?
ASHLEY:
It's just not working.
- JOSH: Why would it do that?
- ASHLEY: I don't know.
- (rumbling)
- Whoa! What is that?
(rumbling continues)
ASHLEY: Oh. my God.
What is that?
(panting)
- Josh. I don't like this.
- JOSH: Hold on. wait.
Just stay still.
Where is it coming from?
ASHLEY: I don't know.
- Oh!
- JOSH: Ashley.
Oh. my God.
(humming)
JOSH:
Oh. my God.
(rumbling)
Josh.
(Ashley screaming)
JOSH: Ashley. run! Run!
(static)
JOSH:
Oh. my God!
- Get down! Get down!
- ASHLEY: Ow!
JOSH:
Run!
(Ashley continues screaming)
(wind gusting)
JOSH:
Jesus Christ! Whoa.
Holy shit. Oh. my God.
ASHLEY:
Oh. my God.
(breathes shakily)
Josh? Josh?
- Are you okay?
- JOSH: Yeah. you?
Yeah.
JOSH:
Your hands are shaking.
I'm scared.
- JOSH: What was that?
- I don't know.
- (rustling)
- (Ashley gasps)
Oh. Mark! Are you all right?
JOSH:
Mark. tell me you saw that. man.
I saw the car.
- You saw the what?
- I saw the car. It's close.
JOSH:
You saw the car?
- ASHLEY: What are you talking about?
- MARK: Come on.
- ASHLEY: Mark. where are you going?
- MARK: I don't know.
MARK: Can we just get
the hell out of here. please?
- ASHLEY: No. wait!
- JOSH: Mark!
- Mark!
- MARK: Let's go!
ASHLEY:
Okay. Mark. slow down!
- JOSH: Tell me you saw that. man.
- ASHLEY: Hey.
MARK: Can we just get
the hell out of here. please?
ASHLEY: I think we should have
a group huddle first.
JOSH:
Mark. what was that?
Come on. man. what did you see?
Josh. I need you to stop talking
until we find the car.
ASHLEY: Okay. You're sure
the car's over here?
MARK:
Yes. I'm positive the car's over here.
JOSH (laughing): Can we please
talk about what we got on tape?
ASHLEY:
Oh yes!
- MARK: I told you.
- ASHLEY: The car!
Oh. Oh!
(panting)
ASHLEY:
Thank God.
MARK:
We're not gonna see anything. Josh.
(Josh chuckling)
MARK:
Josh. get your ass in the car.
JOSH: Ah. come on.
what if they come back?
I swear to God
I'll leave you. Let's go.
- JOSH: Just five minutes. man.
- Come on. Get in the car.
- (exhales deeply)
- ASHLEY: You really didn't see anything?
I thought I did.
I thought I saw these. um...
- JOSH: Like circles?
- No. dumbass. Like rings.
And they were above me.
and then they were gone.
Wait. rings like the petroglyphs?
Did you guys not see these?
All right. it was obviously
in my head. all right? Let's just go.
- (console beeping)
- (engine sputtering)
(long beep)
ASHLEY:
Oh shit. Oh shit.
- (engine starts)
- JOSH: There we go.
ASHLEY:
Oh. thank God.
You guys. what the hell
just happened to us?
JOSH: No one has ever filmed
anything like that before.
Let's just get out of here.
- (pop music playing on radio)
- MARK: Signs of civilization.
ASHLEY: I know.
It feels so nice to listen to music.
MARK:
You're gonna be real famous. Josh.
- ASHLEY: I think he will be.
- JOSH: Thank you.
MARK:
Yeah. until they think it's all faked.
(pop music plays on radio)
- Are you okay. Mark?
- MARK: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: Are you sure?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
ASHLEY:
Your head feels a little bit hot.
Yeah. I have a stomachache.
but I'm good.
(static on radio)
JOSH: I think Mark's gonna be
the most famous
when people see
how bad he pissed his pants.
- (Ashley laughing)
- MARK: Dude. shut up. Are you serious?
- ASHLEY: Mark. you were really scared.
- MARK: I would have loved to see
- either of you up there by yourselves.
- ASHLEY: You should have seen your face.
Okay-
(static on radio)
JOSH:
What's up with the radio?
(static continues)
- I have to drive for two hours.
- JOSH: All right. all right. all right.
MARK:
And we're done shooting.
Whoa. whoa. what is that?
- MARK: What?
- ASHLEY: Is that a car?
- What is that?
- MARK: What the hell is that?
JOSH:
It's just a car.
ASHLEY: No. no. no.
there's no way on earth.
MARK: Josh. cars don't have
one light. What is that?
Is it getting clo... turn that off.
ASHLEY: Sorry.
- Okay. Mark. speed up. Go. go. go. go. go.
- MARK: I am.
- (engine revving)
- MARK: Josh. is it getting closer?
ASHLEY:
Yeah. it's getting closer. I can see it.
- Oh. my God.
- MARK: What the hell is that?
Josh. it's not a car!
MARK:
Josh. what's it doing? What's it doing?
- Is it getting closer?
- ASHLEY: Oh. my God. it's right behind us!
Mark. speed up!
Go. go. go. go. go!
MARK:
I'm going as fast as I can!
(all scream)
- JOSH: Don't stop. dude!
- My car just died!
- ASHLEY: Oh. my God. I don't like this!
- MARK: What just happened?
What just happened?
The car isn't going.
What the hell just happened?
ASHLEY (whispering):
Josh.Josh.
- MARK: What the heck!
- ASHLEY: Okay. stop.
Uh. everything was fine with the car.
and now... it's not.
The engine doesn't have power.
The whole car in general
doesn't have power.
(Spits) Ah.
My mouth tastes weird.
JOSH: Adrenaline.
It's why your mouth tastes weird.
(beer can pops)
No water.
Yo. Josh. come help me.
JOSH: Cool.
MARK:
Ash. put the E-brake up.
There we go. You ready?
Let's go.
(both grunting)
JOSH:
What the hell is going on. man?
MARK:
I don't know. man.
All right. that's good. Ash.
- JOSH: Mark?
- Yeah?
JOSH:
Hey. man. you all right?
- Yeah.
- JOSH: Dude. Dude. your nose is bleeding.
ASHLEY:
What's going on?
- What happened?
- I just have a nose bleed.
- ASHLEY: What?
- I'm fine.
- JOSH: You okay?
- Yeah.
I used to get 'em all the time
when I was a kid. Stop.
- JOSH: Oh. my God.
- It is the dry air.
- You're sweating.
- I'm fine.
- Is it any better?
- Oh.
Here.
How far do you think
the gas station is?
- Mark?
- Uh. seven. eight miles.
JOSH:
In the dark?
We should stay with the car.
we're not doing that. That's crazy.
Yeah. we are. No. honest.
it'll take a couple hours.
it'll be open.
we'll get some help.
- Let's go. Josh?
- Come on.
- JOSH: Ashley. this is crazy.
- (Ashley sighs)
JOSH:
Shoot.
- JOSH: You all right?
- Huh?
You cool?
- You all right?
- ASHLEY: Hey. guys.
- JOSH: Yeah.
- ASHLEY: Come on.
(Winces)
(shuddering)
You guys. it's getting cold.
JOSH:
Hey. Ash?
Let's let Mark catch up.
Something's wrong with him. Josh.
- JOSH: It's. uh. just a nose bleed.
- No.
It's not just a nose bleed.
I mean. something happened
to him up there.
It's not just a coincidence. the car dying
right when the lights came back.
JOSH: So what are you saying?
They're messing with us?
They're following us.
MARK: Guys!
Do you hear that?
- Did you hear that?
- ASHLEY: Hear what?
Come here.
ASHLEY: Mark. come on.
MARK:
No. someone's out there.
(shouting) Hey!
- ASHLEY: Mark!
- MARK: Come... come here! Come help us!
ASHLEY:
Dude. come on!
MARK:
Come help us!
- What is he talking about?
- MARK: Dan. I can hear you.
- JOSH: Mark!
- ASHLEY: Mark!
Shh.
Dan! Thank God!
- ASHLEY: What? Do you hear anything?
- MARK: Guys. it's my brother!
How did you find us?
ASHLEY:
What the hell is he talking about?
- JOSH: Mark! Come on!
- ASHLEY: Mark!
JOSH! Mark. come on!
(rumbling)
JOSH:
Whoa! Jesus! Ashley!
ASHLEY: Mark!
(wind gusting)
ASHLEY (whispering):
What was that?
JOSH: I don't know.
OW! Ah! Ah!
(panting)
- Mark!
- JOSH: Mark! What the hell?
Mark!
ASHLEY: Hey. Mark!
I can't see his headlamp.
JOSH:
Mark?
Come on. man.
Hold on.
(clicks)
- Did you hear anything?
- ASHLEY: No.
JOSH: 'Cause Mark said
he heard voices.
ASHLEY: What voices. Josh?
There's no one out here.
Let's just find Mark.
Hey. Mark!
JOSH:
He looked so sick. Mark?
How much further
could he have gone?
- JOSH: I don't... I don't know.
- ASHLEY: Mark!
Mark!
JOSH:
Oh. God.
ASHLEY: We're not going anywhere
until we find Mark.
Mark!
- JOSH: Ashley.
- No. we're gonna find him.
JOSH:
Ashley.
ASHLEY:
Mark!
- (sobbing) He's gone.
- He's not gone.
He's not gone.
He's just...
He's just lost.
He's just lost. okay?
What are you talking about?
He was there.
and then he was gone.
Something took him.
They took him.
No. No one took him.
He's probably behind
one of these hills. Okay?
- But we... we've gotta keep moving.
- (continues sobbing)
We've gotta keep moving.
we've gotta find people.
We can come back and help Mark. all right?
So come on.
Come on. Please.
- Okay.
- All right. all right.
Okay-
All right. I'm okay. I'm okay.
JOSH: Listen...
don't worry about him anyway.
Okay? He's been in...
the Boy Scouts
since he was like two years old.
- ASHLEY: Mark!
- JOSH: And he's go...
Holy shit!
- What? What is it?
- Look! Look. it's a light!
- ASHLEY: Is it them?
- JOSH: No!
That's like... like a street light
or a trailer or something.
I told you.
Okay. Let's go.
JOSH:
We can get some water. Call for help.
ASHLEY:
Let's go. Yeah.
- ASHLEY: Are you still filming?
- Yeah.
I'm trying to film landmarks
so we can retrace our steps.
ASHLEY:
That's smart.
I think I just need
a second to rest.
We're gonna be okay.
We're gonna find him. Josh.
JOSH: Yeah.
(Josh coughs)
- ASHLEY: Shit!
- What?
ASHLEY: Damn it!
I just dropped my flashlight.
JOSH:
Okay. where is it?
No. there's no way
we can get it. Look down.
Shit!
JOSH: Okay. we're gonna
use this as a flashlight.
Okay. just flash it
in front of me. all right.
- ASHLEY: Okay.
- JOSH: Don't drop it.
- ASHLEY: All right.
- Okay. let's go.
ASHLEY: Whoa.
How long does this battery last?
JOSH:
About an hour.
ASHLEY:
Oh. shit.
JOSH:
Is it bright enough?
ASHLEY:
Yeah. it's okay.
JOSH:
We're almost down.
ASHLEY (gasps):
Josh?
JOSH:
What?
God. Oh. my God.
(shivering)
I have t... I have tissues.
Get 'em. Where's... where's...
- It's in my front pocket.
- JOSH: The front pocket?
Here. Here. Here.
Okay-
JOSH: I shouldn't have brought
you guys out here.
It's not your fault.
I wanted to come.
Why?
I don't know.
I just wanted to do something different.
Something unexpected.
Something my dad
wouldn't expect. anyway.
I'm good.
- JOSH: You sure?
- Yeah. I'm good.
I'm good. Come on.
(Ashley coughing)
(thump)
JOSH:
Shit. Ashley?
(coyotes howling. screeching)
ASHLEY: Shit.
Let's go.
JOSH: Okay.
(flies buzzing)
JOSH:
Oh. God.
- Josh.
- Hey.
Hey. we can't go back.
Come on.
Just don't look at 'em.
- Shit.
- ASHLEY: They're burned.
They burned them.
ASHLEY: Ah!
Ashley?
Josh?
- JOSH: It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
- (Ashley crying)
JOSH:
It's okay.
- ASHLEY: Do you hear that?
- JOSH: Hear what?
ASHLEY:
Do you hear that?
JOSH:
Ashley?
You don't hear that?
JOSH:
Ashley?
- ASHLEY: It's my dad.
- JOSH: Ashley?
- (rumbling)
- JOSH: Oh!
- It's my dad! (laughing)
- JOSH: Oh. my... Oh. my God!
- Ashley!
- ASHLEY: Dad!
- Dad!
- JOSH: Oh!
ASHLEY:
I'm right here!
- JOSH: Ashley. stop!
- Dad. I'm here!
I'm right here!
- JOSH: Ashley. don't!
(explosion)
It's my dad!
(laughing) It's my dad!
(laughing) Dad!
(wind gusting)
Ashley. stop!
Dad!
(static)
(Josh panting)
(rumbling)
Hello!
(panting continues)
(groans)
(glass shatters)
(screaming)
(screaming continues)
(explosions)
(static)
(wind blowing)
(birds chirping)
(ominous music playing)
(classical score playing)